We're playing, Never Have I Ever Lesbian Edition!
我们在玩，“我从来没有”女同性恋版！
No, we forgot the "couples"
不，我们忘了是“情侣”版
You and I are just friends
你和我只是朋友
Today, we are playing Never Have I Ever
今天，我们玩的是“我从来没有”
Lesbian Couple Edition
女同性恋情侣版
We've been living together for like a year
我们一起生活了一年
and we've been together for around three years, and..
我们在一起已经三年了，而且...
You've always forget our anniversary
你总是忘记我们的周年纪念日
We don’t have an anniversary
我们没有周年纪念日
No, we don’t have an anniversary
不，我们没有周年纪念日
So, we've been in a relationship for four years
所以，我们交往已经四年了
Okay, we pretty much moved in together straight away
好的，我们几乎立刻就搬到了一起
so, we're the co-parents of dogs as well
而且，我们也是狗的共同父母
Not cats.
不是猫
This is Lola.
这是萝拉
And this is Sirius! Yay!
这是小天狼星！ 耶！
I'm Lola, don’t get it confused, don't get it twisted
我是诺拉，别弄混了，别搞错了
Never have I ever…
我从来没有过...
Gone over to my girlfriends house for a sleepover and never left
去我女友家过夜却没走
Does it count if it's my house?
如果是我的房子算吗？
It's called moving in together
叫做一起搬家
I feel like it literally was, "Let's sleep over" and then
我觉得这就像是，“让我们睡一会儿”然后
I never left. -  You never left
我没离开。 -你没离开
I never left
我从未离开
Never have I ever…
我从来没有过...
shared the same undies
分享同样的内衣
Three, two, one
三，二，一
I have. - I have
我有  -我有
I hope they are clean
我希望他们是干净的
We have a lot of pair of black undies, and it's hard
我们有很多黑色内裤，而且很难
Yeah, it's hard
To know whose is whose
是的，很难
去知道哪个是谁的
Like you'd think it'd be obvious, but it's not
就好像你觉得这很明显，但事实并非如此
It's fine. It's gone in a washing machine
好吧。 它在洗衣机里消失了
It’s economical.- Yes!
很经济。-是的！
It's not like let's trade the same damn pad
这不是让我们交换相同的东西
Or the same tampon
或者同样的卫生棉
That's not making it into the video is it?
这是不能被录进去的，不是吗？
It's an underwear
这是内衣
When times are tough, I guess I've taken one or two of your undies
当困难的时候，我想我已经拿走了你的一两件内衣
But I have better undies, so…
但是我有更好的内衣，所以...
And I have more
我还有更多
You know what? That's a bonus
你知道吗？ 这是奖励
At least we can share things
至少我们可以分享东西
Yeah
是的
Like clothes. -Save money
就像衣服。 -很省钱
Makeup, yeah, we're being
化妆，是的，我们是
Economical. -Economical
经济实惠的。 -经济实惠
Never have I ever
我从来没有
Had my cycle synchronized
我的周期是同步的吗?
Three, two, one, we both know the answer to this
三，二，一，我们都知道答案
Have
已经
Well, my period is like, the wild west
嗯，我的时代就像蛮荒的美国西部一样
It does whatever it wants and it appears like
它想做什么就做什么，看上去就像
every two weeks or every six years, so…
每两周或每六年一次，所以...
Never have I ever been asked
从来没有人问过我
"Who's going to wear the dress at the wedding?"
“婚礼上谁来穿婚纱？”
Oh, god
哦，天啊
Three, two, one
三，二，一
Yes!
是的！
Every day of our lives
我们的每一天
All the time
每时每刻
We meet people, they ask us
我们遇到别人，他们会问我们
"Who's the man in the relationship?"
“谁是恋爱关系中的男人？”
"Who's gonna wear the suit?"
“谁穿这套西装？”
"Who's gonna wait at the end of the aisle?"
“谁等待在婚礼走道的尽头？”
Does it really matter?
这真的重要吗？
Um, no. I have not, thankfully
呃，不。 幸好我没有，谢天谢地
But I think people kinda vibe that we're not like super duper wedding vibes
但我觉得人们会觉得我们不像极好的婚礼
Well, I wanna wear two things at our wedding
我想在婚礼上穿两件衣服
I want to walk down the aisle, in a beautiful wedding dress
我想穿一件漂亮的婚纱走在过道上
potentially lace, you know, so you can see everything
若有若无的蕾丝花边，你知道，所以你可以看到所有内容
And then it all tears away and I'm wearing like a…
然后全部撕掉之后，我穿得就像...
Well fitted suit
很合身的西装
Because I look hot in them
因为我看起来很性感
With like a cape or something
像披风什么的
But probably both of us, I already told her
但我们俩都有可能，我已经告诉过她
If we do get married, she has to wear something tight and sexy
如果我们真的结婚了，她必须穿紧身性感的衣服
But obviously it's her choice
但很明显这是她的选择
It's gonna be a big thing, I feel sorry for the designer
这将是一件大事，我为设计师感到抱歉
It's, you know, gonna be a lot
你知道的，将会有很多
Never have I ever
我从来没有
Had a fight over who wears which item of clothing
为谁穿哪件衣服而争吵
Three, two, one
三，二，一
We litterally did it two minutes ago
我们两分钟前就发生过这样的事
Yeah, it happens on the daily
是的，每天都会发生
I think we have. - No
我想我们有。 -不
We're pretty good
我们很好
Well, see the thing is she just takes my clothing, and it then belongs to her
好吧，看来她只是拿走了我的衣服，然后就属于她了
I don’t think we've ever fought over it
我认为我们从来没有为此争吵过
No, because we have so many clothes
不，因为我们有很多衣服
Actually, we can show you our wardrobe, if you like
事实上，如果你愿意的话，我们可以给你看我们的衣柜
I mean, I have secret little fights in my head
我的意思是，我脑子里有一些小小的秘密斗争
but I just give them to her, because I love her and they're hers
但我只是把它们给她，因为我爱她，它们是她的
and she looks snuggly
她看上去像是很舒服的依偎着
Never have I ever
从来没有
been asked if we are sisters
被问到我们是否是姐妹
Three, two, one
三，二，一
Thank god
感谢上帝
I mean, surprisingly not. I cannot believe we're never been asked
我是说，令人惊讶的是竟然没有。 我不敢相信没人问我们
Right, cause like
对，因为就像
I mean, now it looks like we could be related
我是说，现在看来我们可以有血缘关系了
Yeah, people should ask
是的，人们应该问
They surely should
他们当然应该
This is the sad reality
这是可悲的现实
On the train, one time
在火车上，有一次
We were just like doing this
我们就像这样
and this woman was asking us what the next station was
这个女人问我们下一站是什么
and then turned around after the conversation was done
然后在谈话结束后转过身来
it was so dead, and then she goes
她安静了一会儿，然后她说
"Are you guys sisters?"
“你们是姐妹吗？ “
And I'm like, "No,"
我说，“不，”
And Abby's like, "we're dating."
艾比就像这样说，“我们在约会。”
It's like, "emm"
就像，“呃”
I think it's just awkward
我觉得很尴尬
Yeah, cause we don't look anything.
是啊，因为我们什么都没看
I don't think… Glasses confuse people, we both wear glasses
我不认为...眼镜迷惑了他们，我们都戴着眼镜
Comment blow if you think we look alike
如果你觉得我们长得很像，请在下方评论
Okay, never have I ever
好吧，我从来没有
Worn matching outfits
穿了配套的衣服
Three, two, one
三，二，一
Alright, three, two, one
好，三，二，一
She bought us matching witches' hats
她给我们买了配套的女巫帽
She got done by an Instagram ad
她是通过Instagram广告购买的
We have. - All the time, we coordinate our outfits
我们有。 -我们一直在协调我们的服装
Yeah, like I'm in pink today, she's in blue today
是的，就像我今天穿粉色，她今天穿蓝色
It's kinda matching but not really matching
有点匹配但不完全匹配
But if you look at her eye makeup
但如果你看她的眼妆
you'll notice that she's wearing mixture of pink and blue
你会注意到她把粉红色和蓝色融合在了一起
To match her. - To match.
与她相配。 -匹配。
That's what we do
我们就是这么做的
Cause we're a package deal
因为我们是成套交易
Yeah, we are
是的，我们是
Is that a lesbian thing?
那是看起来像是同性恋的事吗？
Yeah, we are.
是的，我们是。
We are like peas in a pod
我们就像豆荚里的豌豆
We are like Tim Tams and chocolate. That's not one
我们就像雅乐思和巧克力。 那不是这样的
雅乐思(Tim Tam®)：澳洲著名的巧克力品牌。
Tea and milk
茶和牛奶
Yep, bacon and eggs. - Yeah!
是的，培根和鸡蛋。 -是啊！
We're like Ariana Grande and music
我们就像阿里安娜·格兰德和音乐
Or high ponytails
或者高马尾辫
You're, okay, you’re forgetting about the time
你，好吧，你忘了那会
we wanted to dress up as Steve and Terri Irwin
我们想打扮成史蒂夫和特里·欧文
史蒂夫和特里·欧文：澳洲Discovery的夫妻档节目
《鳄鱼猎人/The Crocodile Hunter》主持人。
But we just looked like
但我们看起来就像
Lesbian zoo keepers!
拉拉动物园管理员！
Like stereotypical lesbians. - Zoo keepers
就像刻板的女同性恋的形象。 -动物园管理员
It was awful, and nobody got it
太糟糕了，没人知道
No, and it was not good
不，那不是很好
Never have I ever
我从来没有
been asked "who is going to have the kid?"
被问到“谁来生孩子？ “
Three, two, one
三，二，一
Not from memory. No. No baby for me
我印象里没有。 不，我没有，宝贝
Okay, all right
好吧，好吧
You know what, it’s a real shame
你知道吗，真是太可惜了
because I never even got to use this one
因为我从没用过这个
Isn't it so…- It’s a real shame
是不是… -真可惜
that the patriarchy still exisits
父权制仍然存在
and we're still getting asked that question
而我们仍然被问到这个问题
It’s obvious. Like we allude this like
很明显。 就像我们营造的那样
"we're not gonna have children" vibe, or at least I…
“我们不会有孩子”的氛围，或者至少我...
We just don’t care for them
我们只是不在乎他们
I'm the top
我是攻
Nola gets mad flu
诺拉得了流感
Let's hope that no one
希望没有人
Sorry grandma, sorry everyone's parents, but I'm the top
对不起奶奶，对不起大家的父母，但我是“攻”
So as you can imagine, downstairs is pretty closed
所以你可以想象，“下面”很封闭
Now imagine trying to shove a baby out of that thing, it's not gonna work
想象一下把孩子从那东西里挤出来，这是行不通的
It’s not gonna happen, it's not gonna fit
不会发生的，也不适合
I certainly believe that more people should adopt
我当然相信更多的人应该收养
rather than like have more children
而不是喜欢生育更多的孩子
I mean, personal opinion
我是说，个人意见
But I also know that our good friends are gonna have kids
但我也知道我们的好朋友会有孩子的
and be great parents, and I will rock that auntie roll
做伟大的父母，我会充当那个阿姨角色
Yeah, lots of Lego. - Lots of Lego
是的，很多乐高。 -很多乐高
And then we go home, to our childless home
然后我们回家，去我们没有孩子的家
and like, have a rave or go to Europe
就像，去狂欢或去欧洲
We'll live off the pink dollar. - Yeah
我们靠粉色的美元过活。 -是的
We'll just live off that pink, gay dollar
我们就靠那gay粉的美元过活
Yeah, exactly
是的，没错
Althought with your Arts degree
尽管你有文学学位
You shut the hell up about my Arts degree
你把我的文学学位说的一团糟
All right? We're doing very well right now
好吗？ 我们现在做得很好
(Final thoughts) How did you feel about it all?
（最后的想法）你对此有何感想？
Oh, I felt good
噢，我感觉很好
I mean, the questions are, unfortunately so common
我是说，这些问题很常见
The biggest takeaway should be that
最大的收获应该是
our relationship's just like your relationship
我们的关系就像你的关系
There is a lot of emotions
有很多情绪
but I think that's a really good thing
但我觉得这是件好事
Like I think there's so much empathy, and compassion, and listening
就像我认为有足够多的同理心，同情和倾听
Yeah, double the wardrobe
是的，双倍的理解和包容
Boobs to lie on. -Yeah
心与心的相互靠近。 -是的